<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:id="@+id/main"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:padding="24dp"
    tools:context=".TermsActivity">

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="0dp"
        android:layout_height="0dp"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <!-- Title -->
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textTermsTitle"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="Terms and Conditions"
                android:textSize="22sp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:textColor="@android:color/black"
                android:layout_marginBottom="12dp" />

            <!-- Content -->
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textTermsContent"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:text="These Terms and Conditions (“Terms”) govern your use of the MemoroX Notes application (“the App”). By installing or using the App, you agree to follow these Terms.\n\n1. Use of the App\n\nYou may use MemoroX Notes for personal or non-commercial purposes.\nYou agree not to use the App for illegal activities or to store unlawful content.\n\n2. Ownership and Intellectual Property\n\nThe App, its design, name, logo, and all related assets are the property of the developer.\nYou may not copy, modify, resell, or distribute any part of the App without permission.\n\n3. User Content\n\nAll notes you create using the App are stored locally on your device.\nYou are fully responsible for the content you create or store in the App.\n\n- The developer cannot access your notes\n- The developer is not liable for loss or deletion of data from your device\n\n4. Data and Privacy\n\nThe App does not collect personal data.\nFor more information, please see our Privacy Policy.\n\n5. App Updates\n\nWe may update or improve the App over time, including adding, modifying, or removing features.\nSome updates may be required for security or performance reasons.\n\n6. Limitation of Liability\n\nThe developer is not responsible for:\n\n- Any loss of notes due to device issues, uninstalling the app, formatting, or user error\n- Any damages caused by misuse of the App\n- Third-party interference or device malfunction\n\nYou use the App at your own responsibility.\n\n7. Termination of Use\n\nWe reserve the right to suspend or discontinue the App at any time, with or without notice.\n\n8. Changes to Terms\n\nWe may update these Terms occasionally. Continued use of the App after updates means you accept the revised Terms.\n\n9. Contact\n\nIf you have any questions about these Terms, you can contact us:\n\nEmail: petshall.com@gmail.com"
                android:textSize="16sp"
                android:textColor="#444444"
                android:lineSpacingExtra="4dp" />

        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>

</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>
